Dellan Muchengapadare

Software Engineer

South Africa, Cape Town +27637934124 dmuchengapadare@gmail.com Github LinkedIn

SKILLS AND PROFICIENCIES

- Javascript | Node.js | Ruby | Python
- HTML | CSS | Tailwind | React.js | React Native | Next.js | Vue.js
- SQL | NoSQL | Redis
- Git | Docker | CI /CD |
 Terraform | AWS Services

LANGUAGES & SOFT SKILLS

- English (Proficient)
- Team player
- Strong Communication
- Attention to details and strong problem solving skills
- Effective time managment

With over **5 years of experience as a software engineer**, I am a seasoned professional dedicated to delivering high-quality solutions. My passion for coding and problem-solving has driven me to continually expand my skills and knowledge, allowing me to excel in diverse technical environments.

WORK HISTORY

Senior Software Engineer

Tatango Inc - North Carolina | April 2021 - May 2023

- Migrating legacy Ruby on Rails codebase to the latest technologies such as React.js, Node.js AWS serverless
- Contributed to building an automated deployment pipeline with AWS CDK and this improved the companies feature delivery rate

Senior Software Engineer

Tupublish Inc - Denver Colarado | Jun 2020 - April 2021

- Developed, installed, and configured internal applications, as well as new application releases into test and production environments.
- help build and ship a multi-purpose social media web application for writers

Junior Frontend Engineer

Chegin Online Inc - London, UK. | Sep 2017 - May 2020

- Attendance management, check-in-out, and reservation services for a church.
- Implemented the UI in React.js consuming a C# Rest API

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Mechanical Engineering

The University of Zimbabwe | 2020

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

Amazon Web Services | 2023

Google Africa Developer Training Program

Google Inc, 2021